-= CHD字幕组 原创翻译 =-
字幕仅供翻译学习交流 谢绝用于任何商业用途
翻译：FanGhost dahongying Sambug
校对：dahongying
有一段时间了 你看起来不错
It's been a while. You look good.
你是如何跟踪这些人的？
How'd you track these guys, anyway?
我有我的方法
I have my ways.
你要告诉我你的线人是谁吗？
You gonna tell me who your snitch is?
不错的尝试
Nice try.
听着，我只想要特雷弗
Look, I only want Trevor.
你该休息下了
You can have the rest.
你的副手呢？
Where's your gun caddy?
在“三次灼烧之地”被吉普赛人杀了
Killed by gypsies in the Thrice Burned Lands.
被吉普赛人杀了
By gypsies.
你确实看起来不错
You do look good.
你看起来像狗屎，老家伙
You look like shit, old man.
亲爱的，宝贝，听着
Stewie, baby, listen.
我们只是要坚持一段时间
We just gotta stick it out a while longer.
人们会开始想念我们能给他们的
The people will start missing what only we can give 'em.
给我一杯蓝方威士忌，加冰
Yo, give me a Blue Label on the rocks, glass of water.
你认为他们会选择荒漠
Do you think they're gonna choose the wasteland...
而不是舒适的旧世界吗？
over the comforts of the old world?
快从吧台后面滚出来，赏金杀手！
Come out from behind the bar, bounty killer!
另一个赏金通缉令已被九人议会认可了
Another bounty warrant approved by the Council of Nine.
这个死刑令是发给赫伯特·特雷弗·琼斯的
This death warrant is issued for Herbert Trevor Jones,
由于逃税罪，内幕交易罪
wanted for tax evasion, insider trading,
奴役员工罪和战争罪而被通缉
employee slavery and war crimes.
怎么了，特雷弗？
What's the matter, Trevor?
你拿到了个脏杯子？
You get a dirty mug?
# All right tonight #
# Oh, yeah #
# Lookie here #
# Ooh, yeah #
# I don't mind telling you, baby, uhh #
# That you looking kinda good #
玛丽，等等
Mary, Wait.
# Ah, shake that thing, woman #
快点
Ah, come on.
他妈的…
Son of a...
你想抢我的人头？
Are you trying to steal my kill?
只是要帮助一个家伙脱困
Just trying to help a guy out.
你真是麻烦
You're a real pain in the ass.
你知道？
You know that?
哦，好吧，至少我的枪没问题
Yeah, well, at least I don't have gun problems.
把他给我 对
Give me that. Yeah.
我也许应该给自己找一个副手
I should probably get myself a gun caddy.
- 你准备拉我起来？  - 不
- You gonna pull me up? - No.
在不远的将来
In the not-too-distant future,
世界列强已经屈服于大企业
the world powers were brought to their knees by big business.
被权利和贪婪所推动
Fueled by power and greed,
工业巨头们拿起了武器
the great titans of industry took up arms
并开始相互毁灭
and set out to destroy one another,
升级到企业战争
giving rise to the corporate wars.
这个国家在漩涡中沉沦并被遗忘
As the nation spiraled into oblivion,
企业高管们解雇了他们的军队
the top executives abandoned their armies
携带着世界剩余的财富逃跑
and escaped with the remainder of the world's wealth.
世界上的大城市战火纷飞已有数年
The great cities of the world burned for many years.
九人赏金议会在废墟中诞生
Born from the ash was the Council of Nine,
发誓重建和带来希望
who vowed to rebuild and give hope
为了荒漠的幸存者
to the survivors of the wasteland.
为了报复公司不计后果的破坏
To avenge the corporations' reckless destruction,
赏金议会颁发死刑令给所有的白领罪犯们
the Council issues death warrants for all white-collar criminals.
由此，一种新型雇佣猎人诞生了
In turn, a new breed of mercenary hunters spawn,
赏金杀手
the bounty killer.
从野蛮的吉普赛人到优雅的刺客
From savage gypsy to graceful assassin,
赏金杀手们争夺人头数
the bounty killers compete for body count,
名气和厚厚的钞票
fame and a fat stack of cash.
他们正在结束这因企业贪婪而带来的瘟疫
They're ending the plague of corporate greed
并给幸存者提供复仇的帮助
and providing the survivors of the apocalypse with retribution.
他们是新时代的英雄
These are the new heroes.
这是赏金杀手的时代
This is the age of the bounty killer.
- 我们爱你！ - 爱你
- We love you! - Yes!
你都不知道你在说什么，亨利
You don't know what you're talking about, Henry.
这看起来像人类的救世主吗？
Does this look like the savior of mankind?
死神玛丽？ 不，这就像是厌女症
Mary Death? No, it looks like misogyny.
你知道什么是厌女症？
Do you know what misogyny is?
不，你不知道，因为漂流者看起来像是这个世界的英雄
No, you don't, because Drifter looks like the hero of the world.
我应该给当副手
I should gun caddy for him.
我要给他当副手
I'm gonna go gun caddy for him.
再见，呆子
So long, suckers.
天堂再见
See you in another life.
打扰一下，漂流者先生，长官
Excuse me, Mr. Drifter, sir,
我听说你需要一个副手
I hear you're in need of a gun caddy.
我是这在这“三次灼烧之地”最快的副手
I am the fastest gun tosser this side of the Thrice Burned Lands,
我也…
and I...
好吧，只准赏金杀手进入
Right, bounty killers only.
听着，我能做任何你让我做的事情
Look, I can do anything you need me to do.
我… 我会槽枪膛 我有全局视野
I...I can flute a barrel. I can globe a sight,
单动作能触发刀刃
trigger a blade for single action,
双动作，三动作，多重动作
double action, triple action, round action.
我可以做任何事情！
I can do anything!
我会莫尔斯电码
I know Morse code.
滴嗒嗒，这是S
Boop-boop-boop.That's an S.
我教会自己如何给打领带
I taught myself how to tie knots.
- 漂流者！漂流者！  - 我会钓鱼
- Drifter! Drifter! - I can fish.
比利·布鲁姆，“荒漠新闻”
Billy Bloom, "Wasteland News."
那么你为什么在这里？看起来像个菜鸟
So what do you got there? Looks like a fresh kill.
你知道我不接受采访的，比利
You know I don't do interviews, Billy.
他确实不接受采访，比利…
He doesn't do interviews, Billy...
- 别这样  - 所以回去吧
- Come on. - so just back off.
- 别这样  - 先预约
- Come on. - Set up an appointment.
像你这样的就应该找一些小的公关来
Guy like you could use a little PR.
这样一个伟大的专题能使你
A great story like this could put you
成功的回到属于你的巅峰
right back up on the top where you belong.
来吧，帮帮我
Come on. Help me out.
我不需要一整页的照片来证明我在工作
I don't need a bunch of front-page photos to prove I'm doing my job.
我的天，她来了！
Oh, my God, she's here!
真的是她！
It's really her!
# Bounty #
# Bounty killer's gonna get ya #
似乎我的专题刚刚抵达
Looks like my story just arrived.
他们去哪？
Where are they going?
他们不知道真正干实事的在这里
They don't know the real deal's right here.
看起来还是妓女的吸引力更大啊
Some broad in hooker boots.
# I want to die in your arms #
# Have you slay me in your bed tonight #
# Killer #
# Cause there's a war going on... #
耶，死神玛丽！
Yay, Mary Death!
我爱你们 我的粉丝就是我的一切
I love you. My fans mean everything to me.
我就像一个优秀的调酒师
I am like a fine sommelier,
我会选择正确的武器去杀人
and I will choose the right weapon for the kill.
一个调酒师，呵呵？
A sommelier, huh?
是的 抱歉 这就像酒…
Yeah. Sorry. It's like a wine...
我知道，我知道那是啥
Yeah, I know what it is.
玛丽，今天数据非常漂亮
Mary, pretty big score today.
你是怎么找到这些黄领带的
How did you find these Yellow Ties...
当其他赏金杀手放弃的时候？
when the other bounty killers had given up?
现在，比利，你知道从不在重要猎杀中退出
Now, Billy, you know I never pull out before the big kill.
我对赏金议会发了誓
I made an oath to the Council...
在它隐藏的地方铲除腐败
to root out corruption where it hides...
也把公正带给你们人民
and serve the justice to you, the people.
你可以引述我这句话
And you can quote me on that.
她真迷人
She is fantastic.
无论如何
Anyways...
不！我刚才是开玩笑的
No! I was kidding.
我应该如何处理这个孩子抽搐的傻逼？
And what am I supposed to do with this twitching twat?
他还没死！
He isn't dead yet!
去他妈的！
Fuck sake!
给你 拿走你的钱
Here. Take your money,
滚蛋吧，你们两个白痴
and piss off, you pair of wankers.
哦，非常感谢
Oh, thank you very much.
漂流者
Drifter.
怎么？
Yeah?
拿去，你个骚货
There, you cunt.
他怎么回事？
And what's his problem?
举止不文明
Bad manners
而且脸涂得让他妈恨不得要去拿锤子
and a face that'd make his mum reach for a hammer.
这么远的东边不经常有吉普赛人
Don't usually get gypsies this far east.
他们搜捕一个隐藏在某个洞穴里的绿领带
They raided a Green Tie hideout at some caves
就在这里南边
just south of here.
偷走了所有孩子并把他们洗脑成为疯狂的杀手
Stole all the kids to brainwash 'em into raving-mad killers.
确实，吉普赛人是血淋淋的动物
Bloody animals, really, the gypsies are.
小费还算不错 每次都是两成
Good tippers, though. 20% every time.
噢，见鬼
Oh, bleeding hell.
噢，又一个无头尸
Oh, another headless wonder.
拜托 没有该死的头我怎么确认身份？
Come on. How am I supposed to ID 'em without a fucking head?
放松，威利 我已经弄到了他的公司名片
Relax, Willy. I've got his business card.
这不是一堆垃圾又是什么
Pile of crusted rubbish is what it is.
噢，它闻起来就像一个死胖子的腐烂的蛋蛋
Oh, and it smells like a fat man's rotten yarballs.
我应该扣除少了头的钱
I shall have to deduct some money for the lack of head.
你不如给我一堆狗屎，威利
Are you giving me shit, Willy?
这很简单，你个傻蛋
It's simple, you silly sod.
没有头，没有奖金
No head, no bounty.
你不知道赏金议会是有多么的恼火
You have no idea how far up my ass the Council is
关于这些无头的尸体
about the state of these bodies.
嗯，你知道你可以告诉他们在哪里扔掉它
Well, you know where you can tell 'em to shove it.
现在，不要在这里亵渎赏金议会
Now, don't you blaspheme the Council in here,
否则你的下场就像你的朋友哈瑞一样
or you'll end up like your pal Harry.
哈瑞？
Harry?
谁是哈瑞？
Who's Harry?
死神玛丽，你的天使般的面容真养眼啊
Mary Death, your angel face is a sight for these weary eyes.
谢谢，威利，不过我可不是天使
Thanks, Willy, but I'm no angel.
好吧，菊花一紧呐
Well, pickle my todger.
死神玛丽带来的另一堆公义
Another pile of justice from Mary Death.
那么谁是哈瑞，每个人都这么野蛮？
So who's this Harry, everyone's so wild about?
把它给我
Give me that.
噢，又是什么大生意？
Oh, what's the big deal?
他只是某个无足轻重的白领
He's just some small-time collar.
等等 这是你的线人？
Wait a minute. Is this your snitch?
不是
No.
他是
He is.
很有趣
Very interesting.
让他走
Just let it go.
好吧
All right.
- 我是认真的  - 算是吧
- I'm serious. - Okay.
他都是你的
He's all yours.
暴躁狂
Crabby.
嘿，对不起 我只是…
Hey, sorry. Just...
我了个去！
Holy shit!
我只是想说我是从未有过的最好的副手
I just wanted to say I'm the best gun caddy ever.
如果你会给我一次机会去证明的话
If you would just give me one chance to prove it.
见鬼，小子
Bloody hell, kid.
你认识这个傻逼？
You know this knob shiner?
只是你做的事情意义如此重大
It's just that what you do means so much,
我也想成为其中一员
and I want to be a part of it.
噢，租用这个员工，你会好得多
Oh, you'd be better off hiring one of these working stiffs.
他有胆量
Ah, he's got guts.
好吧，你以前是谁的副手？
All right, who have you carried guns for?
噢，好问题
Okay, good question.
一，黑色贝蒂，二，怪客布恩
One, Black Betty, two, Cracker Boone,
都是顶级赏金杀手
both top bounty killers.
漂流者，你听到了吗？
Drifter, did you hear that?
黑色贝蒂和怪客布恩
Black Betty and Cracker Boone.
祝你好运，孩子
Good luck, kid.
确保保持新人的激情
Make sure to keep a fresh mag handy,
而且，嗯，永远在他左边
and, um, always stay to his left.
- 没错  - 他就是喜欢这样
- Yep. - He likes that.
威利
Willy.
好吧，好吧
All right, all right.
别让你的咪咪扭曲了
Don't get your tits in a twist.
处理你的尸体总是我的荣幸，亲爱的
Slabbing up your bodies is always a pleasure, my darling.
也是我的荣幸
The pleasure is all mine.
愿上帝保佑你，亲爱的
Bless you, love.
再见
See you around.
漂流者…
Drifter...
让这个笨蛋滚开
get this mangy mutt out of here.
你知道规矩的
You know the rules.
快走，去启动我的摩托
Just go, and gas up my bike.
我们必须要找到哈瑞
We have to go find Harry.
对！
Yep!
噢，我的天
Oh, my God.
我是副手了！
Gun caddy coming through!
我没事！
I'm all right!
我没事
I'm all right.
我只是不小心跌了下
I just fell down a little bit.
我们看见她了，老大
We see her, boss.
我知道做什么，甘利先生
You know what to do, Mr. Gunney.
让她加入或者让她消失
Get her to join up or take her out.
收到
Roger that.
现在，这个牙齿不齐的家伙是你的线人，对吗？
Now, this snaggletoothed guy's your informant, right?
对，他是个坏东西，但他无足轻重
Yeah, he's a bad guy, but he's small-time.
让他活着更有价值
He's been more valuable to keep alive,
因为他常和大人物在一起
'cause he swims with bigger sharks.
- 2号枪  - 2号枪
- Two wood. - Two wood.
所以通过小鱼去抓大鲨鱼
So a small fish to catch a big shark.
散弹枪！
Shotgun!
玛丽说她从来没有抢你的线人
So Mary said she wouldn't go after your fish.
所以你们从来不抢彼此的线人
So you guys don't go after each other's kills.
对，不过这并不是说你就不能
Yeah, but it doesn't mean you can't make it
防着其他坏家伙
hard as hell for the other guy.
现在闭嘴，把12号枪给我扔过来
Now shut up, and throw me the 12-gauge.
世界顶级副手，呵呵？
World's greatest gun caddy, huh?
停止问问题并保持警惕
Stop asking questions and pay attention.
对不起！
I'm sorry!
# Bounty #
噢，真的对不起，孩子
Ah, I'm so sorry, baby.
我知道你该承受这么大的重量
I didn't know you couldn't handle that much weight.
我猜现在我已经改善了整个系统了
I guess I've gotta carry this whole relationship now.
我保证，没有更多的附件了
I promise, no more attachments.
就像妈妈一样
Just like mama.
谢谢，鲍勃
Thanks, Bob.
这是个大热天
That sun is a scorcher.
告诉你为啥，像这种天
Tell you what, days like today
让你错过臭氧层的保护
make you really miss hat ozone layer,
如果你知道我说的什么
if you know what I mean.
死神玛丽，对吧？
Mary Death, right?
你想要签名？
You want an autograph?
不，不过谢谢你的提议
No, but thank you for the offer.
你的朋友怎么了？
What's wrong with your friend?
他太胖了所以坐不下车了？
Is he too fat to get out of the car?
噢，鲍勃？
Oh, Bob?
鲍勃只是… 他只是有点害羞
Bob's just a... He's a little shy.
我叫格雷格·甘利，荒漠度假村的
I'm Greg Gunney, Wasteland Resorts.
我们在构建美好的未来
We're building a brighter future
连续的单套公寓
one condo at a time.
“停止拯救 开始生存”
"Stop surviving. Start living."
是我们的座右铭
It's our motto.
你被赏金议会审核了吗？
You were vetted by the Council?
是的，我是
Yes, I am.
你看，世界正在发展，玛丽
You see, the world is evolving, Mary,
并且，多亏了你，白领阶层正在萎缩
and, thanks to you, the white collars are dwindling,
因此赏金议会已将注意力转向更高目标
so the Council has turned its attention to loftier goals.
谁赞助你的？
Who's bankrolling you?
我可不会说
I'd rather not say...
不过你来加入我们还不算太晚
But it isn't too late to join our team.
用我们的资源和你的名气
With our resources and your celebrity,
噢，这会是漂亮的合作关系
oh, this could be a beautiful partnership.
如果你不想要签名的话
If you don't want an autograph,
你应该从这儿消失
you need to clear out of here.
有底线的女孩 我喜欢
Bottom-line kind of girl. I like that.
不，格雷格
No, Greg,
你还真是不了解我
you are really not understanding me.
我们已经讨论了很长时间
In the amount of time we've been talking,
大多数女人已经做出决定
most women will have already decided
她们是否想上床还是想成为你的朋友
whether they want to fuck or be your friend.
我可不是大部分女人，格雷格
I'm not most women, Greg.
我只是在决定是想操你
I just decide whether I want to fuck...
还是杀了你
or kill you.
忘了这个婊子，格雷格
Forget this bitch, Greg.
她根本不买账
She ain't buying nothing.
你知道的，鲍勃是对的
You know, Bob's right.
让我们砍掉前戏吧
Let's cut the foreplay.
你认为他们会选择荒漠
You think they're gonna choose the wasteland
而不是舒适的旧世界吗？
over the comforts of the old world?
格雷格，你不会撑太长时间的
Greg, you're not gonna make it much longer,
我可以让你死得容易点
and I can make your death a little easier for you.
你知道他在哪吗？
Do you know where he is?
不知道
No.
好吧，那他的朋友哈瑞在哪？
Okay, what about his pal here, Harry?
操你妈的
Fuck you.
那是什么，格雷格？
What was that, Greg?
你看起来不是很清醒
You're not being very clear.
快说，格雷格
Spit it out, Greg.
滴水岩
Drip Rock.
哪一种笨蛋会藏在自己的酒吧里呢？
What kind of idiot holes up inside of his own bar?
这说不通啊
That doesn't make any sense.
嗯，被列入死亡通缉令的人
Well, being marked by a death warrant
不会是像之前那么有理智的
doesn't give a man any more sense than he had before,
而且有时最安全的地方就是躲在常见的地方
and sometimes the best place to hide is in plain sight
那里没人会发现你
where no one's looking for you.
- 那好吧，开始干吧  - 不，我独自去
- Well, then, let's do this. - Oh, no, I'm going in alone.
- 你说什么？  - 你听见我说的了
- What do you mean...what? - I know you heard me.
是啊，我是听见了 这主意可不好
Yeah, I did hear you. It's a terrible idea.
听着，听着，你得在外面放风
Listen, listen, I need you to keep an eye on things outside,
不管发生什么，呆在外面
and whatever happens, stay outside,
并做好准备随时走人
and be ready to go at a moment's notice.
就像是警戒
Oh, like a lookout.
这下好了
Oh, this is great.
貌似你拿着大家伙呢
Hey, looks like you pulled out the big guns.
你在追踪什么人，玛丽？
Who are you tracking, Mary?
你最好还是赶紧消失吧，比利
You're gonna want to make yourself scarce, Billy.
是吗，错过这次行动？没门
Yeah, miss out on the action? No way.
对于其他人来说任务很艰巨
Make it hard as hell for the other guy.
你好啊，美女
Hey there, pretty lady.
让我们看看你的小短裙里面是什么
Why don't we see what's hiding up your little skirt?
这样你就跑不快了
That ought to slow you down.
糟了
Oh, shit.
这是真的吗？
So is it true?
你就是弗兰西斯·戈尔曼？
Are you Francis Gorman?
我要是说我是无辜的，你肯定以为我在撒谎
I could tell you I was innocent, but you'd assume I'm lying.
永远别相信一个白领 我教过你的
Never trust a collar. I taught you that.
你还没回答我的问题
You didn't answer my question.
通缉令上的是不是你？
Is that your mug on the warrant?
是我
Yeah, it's me.
那个哈瑞是不是你的老搭档？
And Harry here, is he your old business partner?
你杀他，这样他不会出卖你吗？
You kill him so he wouldn't turn you in?
那个第二个太阳又是什么东西？
And what the fuck is Second Sun?
第二个太阳？
Second Sun?
你到底在说什么啊？
What the hell are you talking about?
天啊，他们想要杀我，你个婊子养的！
God, they tried to kill me, you son of a bitch!
我没有杀害哈瑞
I didn't kill Harry.
问问房间味道 他已经死了一星期了
Smell the room. He's been dead a week.
这是个圈套
This was a trap.
我相信过你
I trusted you.
我信任过你
I believed in you.
玛丽…
Mary...
为什么你不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
我之前打算过
I was going to.
只是…
It's, uh...
太复杂了
It's complicated.
我打算去赏金议会
I'm going to the Council.
我得和审判官谈谈
I need to speak to the Judges.
那是自杀
That's suicide.
从没有人曾上诉一份死亡通缉令
No one's ever appealed a death warrant.
议会守卫会把你杀死在门口
The Council Guard'll kill you at the gate.
是的，到了那里我会处理的
Yeah, well, I'll deal with that when I get there.
那我要和你一起去
Then I'm going with you.
你不能单干
You can't do this alone.
你不能来
You can't come.
我不想让你为我冒生命危险
I don't want you risking your life for me.
我不是请求你
That wasn't a request.
你是不会这么容易干掉我的，是不是？
You're not gonna make this easy on me, now, are you?
那还有什么乐趣呢？
Now, where's the fun in that?
去开车，杰克！
Get the bikes, Jack!
该死 该死 该死
Shit. Shit. Shit.
这可是好素材啊，玛丽
Hey, this is great stuff, Mary.
跟你说过离开这里
Told you to get out of here.
是的，可要错我职业生涯的故事吗？
Yeah, and miss the story of my career?
没有机会了！
Not a chance!
和你一起共事很愉快，比利
Been a pleasure working with you, Billy.
能不能别在地上打滚了
Will you stop rolling around on the ground...
去开车啊！
and get the bikes?!
该死
Shit.
你搞什么呢？玛丽！
What the fuck was that? Mary!
你简直就像个孩子！
You are acting like a child!
我要和你一起去赏金议会
I'm going with you to the Council.
你能不能别在顽固下去了？
Will you stop being so stubborn?
你不能再继续这种狂暴的杀戮行为
You can't go on a kill-crazy rampage
每次都是你在疯狂地杀人！
every time you're mad at somebody!
是吗？瞧好了！
Oh, yeah? Watch me!
玛丽，九点钟方向
Mary, on your nine.
后面怎么回事？
What happened back there?
玛丽为什么要干掉我们？
Why is Mary trying to kill us?
她在发脾气
She's having a tantrum.
把家伙放下，伙计
Put the hammer down, man.
她追不上我们的
She can't catch us.
我把她车子的增压器改动了
I modified her boosters.
要是她全速会怎样？
What happens if she engages them?
不清楚 也许会失控的
I don't know. Probably stall out.
不应该发生的啊
That's not supposed to happen.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你停下来干什么，伙计？
What are you stopping for, man?
快走啊！
We gotta go!
好了，她没死 可以走了吗？
Great, she's not dead. Can we go, please?
不能让你一直跟着我，兔宝宝
Can't have you following me, fender bunny.
# doo, doo-wah #
# Doo-wah #
# Handsome #
# Ah, so handsome #
# Gentle and sweet #
# Knocks me off my feet #
# Every time I see him #
# Handsome #
# Handsome man #
# doo, doo-wah #
# I don't even know his name #
# I don't know where he lives #
# But he's still to blame... #
斯特林先生
Mr. Sterling, sir.
等我几分钟
I'll be with you in a minute.
# Ah, so handsome #
# Gentle and sweet #
# Knocks me off my feet #
# Every time I see him #
# Handsome #
先生…
Sir, Mr....
我跟你说过多少次了
How many times have I told you
一定要维护好我们的外表？
the importance of maintaining our appearance?
我们被赏金杀手包围了
We had the bounty killers surrounded.
给我说重点，艾利奥特
Give me the bottom line, Mr. Elliott.
戈尔曼现在在哪里？
Where is Gorman now?
死神玛丽说他们准备要去赏金议会
Mary Death said they're going to the Council.
死神玛丽？
Mary Death?
死神玛丽
Mary Death.
天啊
God.
抱歉离开一下
Excuse me a minute.
什么事，凯瑟琳？
Yes, Catherine?
进展如何了
Tell me our progress.
我们碰到麻烦
Well, we hit a snag.
死神玛丽出现了，并搞乱了我们的计划
Mary Death showed up and ruined our plan.
现在赏金杀手奔向议会而去
Now the bounty killers are headed for the Council.
这是个令人不安的消息，斯特林先生
This is disturbing news, Mr. Sterling.
董事会正在对你失去他们的耐心
The board is losing their patience with you.
那是什么噪音？
What is that horrible noise?
很抱歉有干扰
My apologies for the interruption.
完成任务，斯特林先生
Finish the job, Mr. Sterling.
再有任何散失，你就没有任何机会了
Any more hiccups, and we will have no choice
只好把你终结掉
but to terminate you.
听清楚了吗？
Am I clear?
是的，夫人
Yes, ma'am.
我们得回到起点，假装什么也没发生过
We gotta get back to it, act like nothing happened
留活口
and keep the killing alive.
如果你想退出，我能理解
I'll understand if you want to quit.
我一点也不相信
I don't believe any of this.
我注意了你好几年了
I've followed you for years.
你是我们最好的赏金杀手
You're the best bounty killer we got.
现在其他的杀手都在追杀我
And now all the others are gunning for me.
这对你来说太危险了，孩子
It's too dangerous for you, kid.
不 你给了我一个机会
No. You took a chance on me.
我也要报答你
I'm taking one on you.
所以我要一直和你在一起
So I am with you till the end,
做你的副手
always on your left.
那么我们如何才能到那里？
So how are we gonna get there?
没人知道在什么地方
Nobody knows where it is.
我会找到的
I'll figure it out.
我们首先得穿过荒原
We'll just have to get across the Badlands first.
- 荒原？  - 安静
- The Badlands? - Quiet.
什么情况？
What is that?
把灯灭掉 把灯灭掉
Kill the lights. Kill the lights.
是什么？
What is it?
吉普赛人
Gypsies.
操！吉普赛人？
Fuck! Gypsies?
- 死定了！  - 冷静些
- We're dead! - Calm down.
冷静？赏金杀手是一回事
Calm down? Bounty killer's another thing,
可吉普赛人呢？野蛮割喉、嗜好屠杀的吉普赛人？
but gypsies? Throat-ripping, village-raping gypsies?
快趴下
You get down.
怎么趴？
How down?
他们可能在这附近安置了探子
They probably got scouts all around here.
那是不是摩卡·苏加塔？
Is that Mocha Sujata?
那是吉普赛女王
That's the gypsy queen.
他们说每个看到她的外人都会被杀掉
They say every outsider who sees her gets killed.
是啊，你最好得到她的签名
Yeah, well, you better get her autograph...
在她隔开你喉咙之前
before she slits your throat.
我不要她的签名
I don't want her autograph.
跑到这么远的西部干什么，赏金杀手？
What are you doing this far west, bounty killer?
只有那些想穿越荒原的人才会跑这么远
Only those that want to cross the Badlands come out this far.
我们想要找到圣达罗萨
We're trying to find San Dalloosa.
我听说今晚有猜数游戏
I hear it's bingo night.
那姑娘在哪儿？
Where's the girl?
你在说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
别跟我耍心机
Don't play smart with me.
一个叫鲁丽的吉普赛姑娘数年前从我们营地逃走了
A gypsy girl named Nuri escaped our camp many years ago.
她杀了我的国王
She killed my king.
那她挺厉害啊
Well, good for her.
她逃走是为了去找你
She escaped to look for you.
她提到一个名字叫漂流者
She mentioned the name Drifter.
也许她是一个仰慕者
Well, maybe she was a fan.
彭卡！
Ponka!
也许会带你去某个地方
Well, that might get you somewhere.
快说
Now...
你把她藏在哪里了？
where are you hiding the girl?
滚蛋
Fuck off.
操！
Fuck!
为什么？
Why?
鲁丽在哪里？
Where's Nuri?
不再玩游戏了
No more games.
你知道这个鲁丽女孩在哪里吗？
You know where this Nuri chick is?
我建议你从…
Can I suggest you start...
她在哪里？
Where is she?
我恨吉普赛人
I hate gypsies.
是的 我也是，孩子
Yeah. Me, too, kid.
该死！该死！
Shit! Shit!
该死！该死！他们要吃掉我们！
Shit! Shit! They're gonna eat us!
你能不能小点声？
Will you keep your voice down?
我没法小点声！
I'm not gonna keep my voice down!
他们吉普赛人就这么干的！他们要吃人！
They're gypsies! That's what they do. They eat people!
杰克，他们不会吃任何人的
Jack, they're not gonna eat anyone.
这只不过是吓唬人的神话，懂吗？
It's just a myth they spread to scare people, okay?
- 我想想  - 什么？
- I think. - What?
我太胖了
I'm so fat.
他们会看上我的 我太好吃了
Oh, they're gonna love me. I'm so marbled.
我不会让任何人吃你的，好吗？
I'm not gonna let anyone eat you, all right?
离天亮还有好几个小时
We still got a few hours till daylight.
等等 什么？你有逃跑方法了？
Wait. What? You got an escape plan?
我正在努力
I'm working on it.
而且，像他们那样的喝酒方式
Besides, the way they're going to that roach liquor,
到了早上一定会是疲惫不堪的
they'll be worse for wear in the morning.
这就是你的逃跑方法，是不是等他们宿醉呢？
That's your escape plan, is that they have hangovers?
是的
Yes.
你有更好的方法吗？
Have you got a better one?
没有，至少我的法子还没想出来
No, but at least mine can't be undone with aspirin.
请告诉我你不认识
Just please tell me that you don't know
他们要找的那个吉普赛姑娘
this gypsy girl that they're looking for.
就是死神玛丽
It's Mary Death.
什么？
What?
- 她就是死神玛丽  - 什么？
- It's Mary Death. - What?
跟你说了就是死神玛丽！
Told you Mary Death!
不应该是死神玛丽
It can't be Mary Death.
她甚至都不是吉普赛人
She's not even a gypsy.
为什么你要冒险为了一个要杀死我们的女人呢？
Why are you risking our lives for a woman trying to kill us?!
这事儿有点复杂
It's complicated.
这有什么复杂的？！
What's so complicated about it?!
因为是一个女人
Because it's a woman.
都是很复杂的
They're all complicated.
你爱上她了，对不对？
You love her, don't you?
对不对？
Don't you?
该死！
Shit!
# Now, if you got a women... #
几年前我第一次遇到玛丽
I first met Mary many years ago...
她跟踪我来到“干燥海狸”
when she tracked me to the Thirsty Beaver,
一个仓库，白天赏金杀手在那里训练
a warehouse where bounty killers could train all day...
到晚上一起分享烈酒
and at night share a stiff drink...
还有一个叫卢西尔的酒吧姑娘
with one of Lucille's famous beaver girls.
# I know a good woman can mean a good man's doubt #
# Ain't that right? #
出去
Get out.
- 快点  - 快点
- Come on. - Come on.
快走
Let's go.
我没有点过吉普赛女人
I didn't order a gypsy.
姑娘们去哪儿了？
Where are the girls?
在你喉咙上有一把刀
You have a blade against your throat,
而你所关心的却是那些婊子吗？
and all you're worried about are those whores?
是啊
Well, yeah.
付的是过夜的钱
Paid for all night.
你是谁？
Who are you?
吉普赛人叫我鲁丽
The gypsies call me Nuri.
如果知道我的下落，他们会杀了我
They'd have my head if they knew I was here.
你逃掉的吗？
You escaped?
他们说在这“三次灼烧之地”你是最好的赏金杀手
They say you're the best bounty killer in the Thrice Burned Lands.
我需要你来训练我
I need you to train me.
为什么你不去
Why don't you get
让你的一个丑脸朋友们来训练你呢？
one of your clown-faced boyfriends to train you?
他们对这个世界已经绝望了
They've given up on the world.
为了彻底遗忘，他们只想烧掉它
They just want to burn it further into oblivion.
你是个合适的人选…
You're setting things right...
而且在这里的确与众不同
and actually making a difference here.
你跟踪我到这里，就是说你有天分
You tracked me here, and that means you got talent.
下来
Get off.
也很有胆量
A lot of spunk, too.
这会很有趣的
Oh, this is gonna be interesting.
总是意想不到啊
Always expect the unexpected.
她无所畏惧地接受了每项挑战
She fearlessly took on every challenge.
我刻苦训练她 我是说你必须得这样
I was hard on her. I mean, you have to be.
你没有说过你会使用实弹射击
You didn't say you were using live rounds.
一定是我忘掉了
Must have slipped my mind.
她进展神速
She was a fast learner.
只要达不到完美就不满足
Anything short of perfection wasn't good enough.
她应该是最好的
She had to be the best.
漂亮
Nice.
我不知道你做完了所有科目
I didn't know you were doing the whole course.
一定是我忘掉了
Must have slipped my mind.
不久我就开始带着她执行任务了
It wasn't long before I started bringing her on jobs.
不错嘛
Not bad.
你想怎么威胁我都可以，宝贝
You can threaten me all you like, love,
但你只能拿到赏金的一半
but half bounty is all you're gonna get.
你得好好考虑一下如何教会她懂礼貌
You'd be well advised to teach that dodgy bint some manners.
那个奸商真是个混蛋！
That merchant is a crook!
这是一个默认的协议而已
It's an unspoken agreement we have.
他们抽取一点赏金
They skim a little bit off top
是为了交换一些消息，懂吗？
in exchange for some information, okay?
不 无法成交
No. Deal, nothing.
当我自己单干时，我就要改变规则
When I'm on my own, things will be different.
你真像是一个孩子
You're acting like a child.
鲁丽，怎么这么吵？
Nuri, what's with all that racket?
我在制作新装配
I'm finishing a new outfit.
而且我再也不叫鲁丽了
And my name isn't Nuri anymore.
我叫“死神玛丽”
It's Mary Death.
那一天，我意识到我已经造就了
On that day, I realized I had created
这个世界上最伟大的杀手
the greatest killer the world would ever know.
我们接下来的几个月是一段很不错的时光
The months that followed were a good time for the two of us.
我们完成了一连串的任务
We pulled off jobs in tandem.
她是我的兔宝宝，我是她的老家伙
She was my fender bunny, and I was her old man.
这个世界已残破不堪，但没有关系
The world was blown to hell, but it didn't matter.
我们战无不胜
We were invincible.
我已经想过了，兔宝宝
I've been thinking, fender bunny.
别说了
Stop talking.
听我说完
You know, hear me out.
你应该得到一个更好的…
You deserve better than a...
在海狸的房间太小了，知道吗？
cramped room at the Beaver, you know?
而且我攒了一笔钱…
And I've saved some money, and...
明天我们就可以开车离开这里…
yeah, we could ride out of here tomorrow...
把这里的一切都抛弃
and leave all this behind.
我们可以开启新的生活
We could start a new life.
该死！你割得够深啊！
Shit! You cut me deep!
玛丽…
Mary...
你割得够深啊！
you cut me deep.
我试过去爱她，小子
I tried to love her, kid,
可她发脾气给了我一刀并丢下我等死
but she stabbed me in the spleen and left me for dead.
你是了解你的吉普赛女人
You really know your gypsies.
估计不能喝太多酒
Can't hold their liquor, I guess.
快走，小子
Move it, kid.
你还在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
我从一群野蛮人那里偷走一辆马车
I'm stealing a stagecoach from of a bunch of savages...
他们像赏金猎人一样在夜间作案
with a wanted criminal moonlighting as a bounty killer,
他们是热衷于杀人，疯狂的吉普赛人
who has the hots for a murderous, deranged gypsy.
梦想成真了，小子
Dreams do come true, kid.
我从未停止过梦想
I never stopped believing.
出发！
Get going!
起来！他们逃走了
Get up! They're getting away.
杀了他们！
Kill them!
胡说
Bollocks.
该死的
Oh, shit.
- 投掷器  - 什么？
- Pitching wedge. - What?
杰克，把投掷器递给我！
Jack, pass me the pitching wedge!
投掷器究竟是什么？
What the hell is a pitching wedge?
角色扮演
The RPG.
我说过让让他们跑掉的
I told you to let them escape.
追上其他人，让他们撤回来！
Catch up with the others, and tell them to fall back!
撤回来！
Fall back!
快点
Oh, come on.
该死
Shit.
炸死你们，混蛋
Boom, motherfuckers.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
我…
Well, I was, um...
我在上面救我们的命
I'm up here saving our necks,
而你在下面的拖车里午睡吗？
and you're down there taking a siesta in the trailer?
他的头碎得到处都是
His head just went everywhere.
是啊，我知道
Yeah, I know.
这太容易了
It was too easy.
容易吗？
That was easy?
怎么是容易呢？
How was that easy?
我不想听这个，杰克
I don't want to hear it, Jack.
赶紧上来，有人有装备 我们得快点走！
Just get up here, and man the rig. We gotta move fast!
我找到一些东西
I found something.
杰克，你刚刚带领我们穿越了荒原
Jack, I think you just brought us a trip across the Badlands.
# Must be an angel #
# You must be my heart #
# Alone in this desert #
# Just let it all start #
# You change like the seasons... #
一打威士忌和可乐得多少钱？
How much for a shot of whiskey and a Coke?
鲁丽？
Nuri?
怎么会是你，卢西尔？
How the hell are you, Lucille?
# Just one more time #
你得喝一杯
You need a drink.
# Forget all the rules... #
天啊，这地方发生什么了？
God, what happened to this place?
我记得每晚我们都在打发顾客的
Man, I remember us turning customers away every night.
我最好的姑娘们都跟着舞蹈团去新凤凰城了
My best girls went off with a dancing show to New Phoenix.
是吗？你为什么不和她们一起呢？
Yeah? Why didn't you go with 'em?
我从来不会跳舞的
Ah, I never was much of a dancer.
总之跟不上节奏
Not on my feet, anyway.
发生了一件奇怪的事
You know, a strange thing happened.
在姑娘们离开后
After the girls left,
这个镇子突然之间失去了活力
this town suddenly lost interest in being a town.
很好奇如何发生的
Funny how that happens.
还喝吗？
Another?
# Must be an angel #
有一个说法，你不能骗傻子
You know, there's a saying you can't fool a fool.
# Must be my heart... #
我知道你是失恋了
I know a broken heart when I see one.
你怎么了，宝贝姑娘？
What's going on with you, baby girl?
# Inside your arms... #
是不是漂流者？
Is it Drifter?
他是其中一个
He's one of them.
他是个罪犯
He's a criminal.
一直以来，他像一条蛇样的躲藏着
This whole time, he's been hiding like a snake.
而现在你却是要杀掉他的那个人，对吗？
And now you're the one who, uh, has to kill him, right?
没错
That's right.
这…
It's, uh...
你很难完成任务
It's hard to do your job
当面对自己心爱的人时
when it goes against what you feel in your heart.
这是人的弱点
It's a weakness.
在你内心还有吉普赛人的性格
Oh, that's just the gypsy in you.
在那层盔甲之下，你仍然是个女人
Underneath that armor, you're still a woman,
有血有肉，像我们一样
flesh and blood like the rest of us.
他对我们撒谎了
He lied to us.
是啊，可他是个英俊的骗子
Yeah, but he's a handsome liar.
来吧 让我给你洗洗
Come on. Let's get you cleaned up.
噢，那是我拍的第一张封面
Oh, hey, that was my first cover.
是啊 我一直保留着
Yeah. I've been keeping track,
我知道早晚你会回来取它的
and I knew you'd come back sooner or later for these.
为此可花费了不少时间啊
Spent so much time working on 'em.
这一张，还不错
Oh, now this one, that's good.
是啊，我的最爱了
Yeah, that's my favorite.
好吧，我一直觉得这个护胸板有点夸张了
Okay, I always thought the chest plate was a bit much.
有时候它对女孩子来说值得使用
Ah, sometimes it pays for a girl to be practical.
卢西尔，你有没有我能用的车子吗？
Lucille, you got a set of wheels I could use?
瞧瞧
Voila.
卢西尔，我爱你
Lucille, I love you.
对，我这个老姑娘还是保持着生命力
Yep, there's still life in the old girl yet.
上周我开出去过，它像头驴子一样
I took her out last week, and she kicked like a mule.
我借用一个防毒面罩
I'm borrowing a gas mask.
是你的了
It's yours.
帮我一个忙
Do me a favor.
如果你杀不掉漂流者，就送到我这里来
If you don't kill Drifter, send him my way.
我会如其所愿来款待这个英俊男人的
I'll give that handsome man all the loving he needs.
你没有变，是不是，卢西尔？
You don't change, do you, Lucille?
为什么要破坏完美呢？
Why mess with perfection?
再会
See you around.
小心点，鲁丽
Take care, Nuri.
你觉得这破车还能开吗？
Think this junker still runs?
这破车可以如同地洞里的蝙蝠一样突然飞起来
Oh, this junker could blow the wings off a bat out of hell.
这是谁的地盘？
Whose place is this, anyways?
“土狼”金波
Coyote named Jimbo.
土狼是什么意思？
What's a coyote?
他从赏金杀手地盘里走私白领出去
He smuggles white collars out of bounty killer territory.
你怎么认识他的？
How do you know him?
你可以说我们有过一段特殊关系
Well, you could say we have a special relationship.
他是你的线人，是不是？对吗？
He's your informant, isn't he? Right?
土狼带着白领到他们认为安全的地方
The coyote takes collars to where they think they're safe.
然后他又返回来告诉你，对吗？
Then he turns around, and he tells you, right. Right?
观察力很敏锐啊，莱曼先生
That's an astute observation, Mr. LeMans.
对不起我曾经低估了你的智慧
Hell, I'm sorry I ever underestimated your intelligence.
谢谢你
Ah, thank you.
等等 什么？
Wait. What?
该死的！漂流者！
God damn it! Drifter!
你他妈的为什么那样敲我的门？
What the fuck are you thinking knocking on my door like that?
你从哪儿搞来的那辆吉普赛拖车？
Where the hell did you get that gypsy trailer?
我们偷来的
Oh, we stole it.
- 什么？ - 从吉普赛人手里
- What? - From gypsies.
你他妈又是谁？
Who the fuck is this?
他是我的副手
Oh, he's my gun caddy.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
进来！
Get inside!
去荒原？
The Badlands?
去它的，伙计
Fuck that shit, man.
不，不，不，我有一个白领
No, no, no, I got...I got a collar
要在新凤凰城去带上
to pick up in New Phoenix.
任务取消吧
Cancel the job.
别碰东西
Don't touch nothing.
没有
Nope.
放弃一个顾客会影响我声誉的
Man, abandoning a client would sully my reputation.
什么声誉啊？
What reputation?
问的好
You know, that's a good point.
你自制燃料吗？
You make your own fuel?
伙计，那可不是普通燃料 那是私酿酒
Man, that ain't no ordinary fuel. That's moonshine.
你用私酿酒来驱动你的车子？
You run your car on moonshine?
对极了，160度酒
Damn straight, 160 proof.
那是一个古老的祖传秘方
That is an old family recipe
又经过我爷爷改良，他叫冈瑟·亚里斯多德·斯通
perfected by my granddaddy Gunther Aristotle Stone.
他真伟大
He was a great man.
为什么你们要急着赶着穿越荒原呢？
Now, why are you in such a rush to get across the Badlands?
又是什么东西？
What's this bullshit?
唱首歌吧
Well, sing a song.
不能说我不奇怪
Can't say I'm surprised, though.
嘿，不能喝那个
Hey, don't drink that.
那酒不是用来喝的
That is not for consumption.
没有 我把它放在这里
No. I'm gonna put it over here.
我要去赏金议会大厦
I'm headed to the Council building.
赏金议会大厦？
The Council building?
伙计，他们一看到你就会开枪的
Man, they're gonna shoot you on sight.
是啊，不过别担心
Yeah, but don't worry about that.
尽管报个价吧
Just name your price.
该死
Oh, hell.
你们不请自来
You show up here not invited.
你还随身带着一个怪胎
You got some weirdo with you.
你是个被通缉的人
You're a wanted man.
你还招惹上了吉普赛人
You been tussling with gypsies.
伙计，金波可是要承担很多风险的
Man, that is a lot of risk for Jimbo to take on.
除此之外，开车穿越荒原
Besides, driving across the Badlands,
可不是周末去郊游，伙计
that ain't no Sunday cruise, man.
那里的辐射很强
The radiation's so hot in there,
在那儿待的时间一长，你的眼珠子就会流血
you stay in there long enough, it'll make your eyeballs bleed.
爽死了，漂流者
Hot damn, Drifter.
你总是给人以惊喜
You are full of surprises.
漂流者的奖品总是很多
Drifter's so full of prizes.
我还没见过六瓶装的啤酒，自从…
I ain't seen a six-pack of PBR since...
这是从谁的冰冷、死亡之手中抢过来的呢？
Whose cold, dead hands you have to wrestle this hooch out of?
有什么关系呢？
What does it matter?
现在是你的了
It's yours now.
该死，漂流者
Damn, Drifter.
你怎么说呢？
What do you say?
我说装上枪支，带上食物，伙计们
I say load up the guns, and pack the biscuits, boys.
我们要开启一场真实的冒险
We are going on a bona fide adventure.
这家伙，太重了
This guy's, uh, sweaty.
你在那酒里究竟掺入了什么东西？
What the fuck did you put in that shit, anyway?
现在可不要小看冈瑟家的秘方了
Now, don't you be railing on Gunther's recipe.
我说过不要喝的
I told him not to drink it.
我希望他别瞎了，别变成阳痿
I hope he don't go blind and his pecker don't fall off.
该死
Shit.
你是个侦察兵
You're a scout.
为什么荒原会有吉普赛人？
Why are the gypsies in the Badlands?
去你的，赏金杀手
Fuck you, bounty killer.
告诉我离开这里的方法
Tell me how to get out of here.
为什么荒原会有吉普赛人？
Why are the gypsies in the Badlands?
鲁丽，他们在寻找你
They're looking for you, Nuri.
啊，糟了！
Ah, damn it!
杰克，杰克
Jack. Jack.
你看
Check it out.
（把所有武器存放进箱里）
（所有武器）
（安全）
好吧
Okay.
这里是哪里？
What is this place?
太好了
Perfect.
多少钱？
How much?
这个，我现在身上没带钱
Okay, look. I don't...I don't have any money on me right now.
我们可不可以作别的交易，我可以…
Um, but if we could work out a deal or something, I could...
不，先生，我不能再回到外面去
No. Look, I...I can't go back out there, sir.
我在请求你的帮助
I'm asking you to help me.
没有地图，我不能再到外面
I can't go back out there without a map.
我不知道如何穿过荒原
I don't know my way through the Badlands.
我需要你的帮忙，显然你是这方面的专家
I need you to help me. You obviously know what you're doing.
你制作地图，我们可以找到解决办法
Look, you make maps. We'll work something out.
如果你能…你在听吗？
If you...Hello?
看着我！
Look at me!
求你了
Please.
我要你的帮忙
I need your help.
什么？
What?
我说过我没有钱
I told you I don't have any money.
谢谢
Thank you.
你该不会刚好有去赏金议会的地图，对吧？
You don't by chance happen to have a map to the Council, do you?
（这里是人间天堂）
（别开飞车）
该死的！我又把荒原甩在身后了！
Hot damn! I whupped the Badlands again!
还刷新了时间记录
And in record time.
你没事吧？
You all right?
你没事吧？检查一下眼球
You all right? Check your eyeballs.
检查一下眼球
Check your eyeballs.
你没事啦
You're all right.
对啊，滚蛋吧，荒原
Hell, yeah. Up yours, Badlands.
我们需要庆祝一下
This calls for a celebration.
现在我可以安乐地死去了
Now I can die a happy man.
杰克，去拿枪
Jack, get the guns.
你绕过去，把剩下的啤酒都保护好
Just go around and get the rest of the six-pack.
你和啤酒
You and beer.
该死
Shit.
好吧，我完蛋了
Well, I'll be damned.
那是谁？赏金杀手？吉普赛人？还是什么？
Who is it? Headhunters? Gypsies? What?
是的，那是个吉普赛人
Yeah, it's a gypsy, all right.
该死
Shit.
是玛丽 该死
It's Mary. Shit.
600码距离
Okay, 600 yards.
那是什么，九号枪？
That's what, the nine iron?
不，我有更好的主意
No, I had a better idea.
你在干什么？
What you doing?
漂流者，她会杀死你的
Drifter, she's gonna take you down.
你在干什么？
Oh, what are you doing?
玛丽！我不再跑了
Mary! I'm done running.
我不再和你争斗了
I'm not gonna fight you anymore.
你是要下来好好聊聊
Are you gonna come down here and talk,
还是继续要敲打我靴子上的泥土呢？
or you just gonna keep knocking dirt on my boots?
你车子的不幸，是我不对
Hey, sorry about your car.
我不知道的 我只是动了一些零件…
I didn't know. I just crossed a few...
喂，喂，放轻松啊
Hey, hey, take it easy, man.
金波，还记得上次见面我跟你说的话吗？
Jimbo, what did I say would happen if I ever saw you again?
你该不会忘记得克萨斯州的事吧？
You ain't still raw about that Texas job, are you?
听着，你是跟我有矛盾，不要拉他进来
Listen, your beef's with me. Leave him out of this.
你已经是个死人了
And you are a dead man.
大伙消停一下吧
Oh, just stop it.
消停一下吧
Just stop it.
我厌倦了这些枪支
I am sick of all the guns
荒原这些破事，还有要吃掉我们的吉普赛人！
and the Badlands and gypsies trying to eat us!
你们被吉普赛人抓住了？
You were captured by gypsies?
是的，吉普赛人抓住了我们
Yes, we were captured by gypsies,
然后他们对这个家伙严刑逼供
and they tortured the hell out of this guy,
但是他没有供出你来
and he never gave you up.
你知道为什么吗？
'Cause you know why?
因为某个操蛋的原因，他爱上了你
For some fucked-up reason, he loves you.
她可以对你乱枪扫射上百万次
And she could have shot you, like, a million times
而她没有
and she didn't,
因为她也爱你
cause she loves you.
所以你们能不能不要再意气用事？
So can you quit acting like children?
求你们了
Please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我们雇佣了金波带路到赏金议会
We hired Jimbo to take us to the Council
让漂流者能和法官们说话
so Drifter can talk to the Judges.
你们永远突破不了赏金议会的防线
You'll never get past the Council Guard.
我跟你说过的
I told you that.
他自有方法解决，好吧？
He's gonna do this his way, okay?
他为了人民做了那么多
After everything he's done for the people,
他有资格面对法官们
he's earned the right to face the Judges.
欢迎你加入我们
And you're welcome to come with us.
什么？
What?
听着，只有我的头颅有悬赏
Listen, I'm the one with the bounty on my head.
你们完全没有理由插手其中
There's no reason for any of you to get mixed up in my mess.
不是你的选择
It's not your choice.
是大家的选择
It's ours.
你准备如何找到去路？
How you gonna find it?
给
Here.
好的，如果我们一路往前走
All right. If we're gonna see this through to the end,
我们总能在终点找到
we're gonna take it the whole way.
我向你们保证一切都会水落石出
And I promise you everything will make sense
只要我们到达了赏金议会
when we get to the Council.
我跟着你们到赏金议会大厦
I'll follow you as far as the Council building,
如果他们判定你有罪
and when they find you guilty,
我将会亲自开枪送你归西
it's gonna be me who puts a bullet in your head.
听起来不错
Sounds like a plan.
总比你的刀插在我的脾要强
It's better than your stupid knife in my spleen.
这不有趣
That's not funny.
我倒觉得挺有趣的
Yeah, it's kind of funny.
就让我们开干吧！
Let's do this!
死了两周
Two weeks.
我们错过了一场大屠杀
We missed one hell of a party.
我只看到赏金议会的守卫
I only see Council Guard.
另一方人的尸体在哪里？
Where are the dead guys from the other side?
他们肯定事后拖走了尸体
They must have dragged 'em away after.
你觉得是谁干的？
Well, who...who do you think did this?
这是“黄色领带”的军队
It was an army of Yellow Ties.
第二个太阳
Second Sun.
这就是他们庆祝的原因
That's why they were celebrating.
玛丽，等一下！
Mary, wait!
我的天
Oh, man.
当我看到我的通缉令的时候
When I saw my warrant,
我就知道出了什么事
I knew there was something wrong.
我要亲眼看一看
I just had to see it for myself.
你怎么知道？
How'd you know?
赏金议会已经知道我的过去
The Council already knew about my past.
他们没有理由
It didn't make any sense for them
过了这么些年才来通缉我
to issue a warrant after all these years.
你认识这些法官？
You knew the Judges?
是的，他们找到了我
Yeah, they tracked me down
在最后一座大都市烧毁以后
after the last of the great cities burned.
他们找到我的那个时候
By the time they found me,
我已经手刃了两个我以前的商业搭档
I'd already killed two of my old business partners.
你为什么要这么做？
Why'd you kill 'em?
我原来的公司是造飞机的
My company built planes,
动荡之后，我的搭档背叛了我
and after the crash, my partners betrayed me
把飞机都卖给了企业民兵团
and sold out to the corporate militias.
他们占领了我的工厂
They took over my plant
开始建造炸弹用以备战
and started building bombers for the war.
每次我听到有城市被摧毁了
Whenever I heard news of a city being annihilated,
我就知道投放炸弹的飞机上
I knew the plane that delivered the bombs
印有我的名字
likely had my name on it.
赏金议会让我做第十名法官
The Council offered me a position as the tenth Judge.
他们需要把认识所有玩家的人安排在内部
They needed someone on the inside who knew all the players,
但是我拒绝了
but I refused.
我已经坐办公室一段时间了
I spent enough time behind a desk.
我需要重操旧业
I needed to get my hands dirty.
所以我成为了第一个赏金杀手
So I became the first bounty killer.
一切都结束了
It's all over.
赏金议会灭亡了
The Council's dead.
人民的希望也随之幻灭了
People's hope will die with them.
不，还没有结束
No, it's not all over.
我们还有一件事要做
We've still got one more job to do.
第二个太阳
The Second Sun.
该死
Ah, shit.
弗朗西斯
Francis.
你好，凯瑟琳
Hello, Catherine.
什么，你认识她？
What, you know her?
真是个遗憾，你不能坚持
It's a shame you didn't stick around...
看着你的公司发挥其潜力
to watch your company fulfill its potential...
和第二个太阳合并
when we merged with Second Sun.
我一直在留意你，追寻你
Oh, I've been watching you for some time and hunting you.
我为悬赏你的头颅感到难过
And I am sorry about putting the bounty on your head.
这太不厚道了，我知道
It wasn't very nice, I know,
但我别无选择
but it was necessary.
你才不难过
Oh, you're not sorry.
你能往你的生母背后插上一刀
You'd stab your own mother in the back...
你的底线本来就无下限
to increase your bottom line.
还有丈夫
Or husband.
应该是前夫
Ex-husband.
你是不是困扰于每个
Are you disturbed by the fact that every woman...
和你有一腿的女人都想杀死你呢？
you've ever been involved with wants to kill you?
这个，好吧，我尽量不想它
Yeah, well, I try not to think about it.
混蛋，你应该早告诉我
Dick-head. You should have told me.
你就是弗朗西斯的小贱人啦
So you're Francis' new little whore.
死神玛丽，大家最爱的赏金杀手
Mary Death, everyone's favorite bounty killer.
我另有计划
You know, I had other plans,
但是既然今天见到你了
but seeing you here today,
好吧…
well...
一切都改变了
That changes everything.
我可以把赏金议会的罪名推到你头上
I'll blame the death of the Council on you.
人民会丧失他们对赏金杀手的信念
The people will lose their faith in bounty killers.
制度会崩溃，然后
The system crumbles, and then...
第二个太阳介入，然后承诺美好的生活
Second Sun moves in promising a better life.
没错
Exactly.
亲爱的，你比你的样子更聪明
Honey, you are smarter than you look.
真遗憾我们要在这种情况下相见
It's a shame we didn't meet under different circumstances.
我们或许能相处下来
We might have gotten along.
如果在不同的情况下
If circumstances were different,
你已经死透透了
you would already be dead.
或许吧
Maybe.
谁知道呢
Or maybe not.
放开你的手别碰她！
Get your damn hands off her!
闭上你的嘴，混蛋
Button your lip, short dick.
老板说话不喜欢别人搭嘴
The boss doesn't like it when people interrupt her.
我罩住你了，凯瑟琳
I got you covered, Catherine.
吉普赛人！
Gypsies!
你得离开这里
You need to get out of here.
那还有什么乐趣呢？
And where's the fun in that?
我认为他们不是跟着我穿过荒原
I didn't think they'd follow me across the Badlands.
他们是冲我而来的，不是吗？
They're here for me, aren't they?
走吧，听着 我们可以让他们互相残杀
Come on, listen. We can let 'em kill each other,
我能带你离开这里
and I can get you out of here.
不 一切就在这里终结
No. This ends right here,
所有一切
all of it.
别再吃枪子了！
Stop getting shot!
对不起要这样对你，金波
Sorry to do this to you, Jimbo.
这种比你再中第三枪好多了
But it's better than you getting shot a third time.
干得好，杰克
Great job, Jack.
把我找到子弹、枪，什么都行
Get me bullets, guns, whatever you got.
我没弹了
I'm out.
杰克，我没弹了
Jack, I'm Out.
你干得出色，小子
You're doing great, kid.
谢谢！
Thanks!
你守着我的左边，我们可以突破重围
Just stay by my left, and we'll get through this.
好啊
Yeah.
我可以放倒那个家伙
I can get that guy.
上膛！该死
Reload! Shit.
不！
No!
和外族人厮混一起，让你变得软弱
Living among the outsiders has made you weak.
你以前是多么出色
You used to be great.
所以国王选中了你
That's why the king picked you.
他竟然以为你比我优秀
He actually thought you were better than me.
他们都是这么想
They all did.
现在我要为国王复仇
Now that my king will be avenged,
我会提着你的首级回归
I'll return with your head
告诉他们我才是真正的皇后
and show them all why I've always been the true queen.
而这就是你的下场…
And this is how you die...
作为赏金议会走狗
as a whore for the Council.
我宁愿以走狗的身份死去
I'd rather die a whore.
天啊
God.
不！
No!
停手！停手！
Stop! Stop!
放松，玛丽，放手吧
Relax. Mary, let go.
放手，没事了
Let go. It's okay.
他们不会伤害你的，好吗？
They're not gonna hurt you, okay?
你还好吧？
You okay?
这些家伙其实也不都是坏人
These guys actually aren't all that bad,
特别是你杀了他们的皇后，他们就…
especially since you killed their queen. They're like...
漂流者在哪？
Where's Drifter?
他被带走了
He's gone.
他们带走了他
They, uh... They took him.
我没有守护着他…
Uh, I didn't stay with him...
像我承诺的一样
like I promised.
我也没有
I didn't either.
我从来没有
I never do.
他保护了我
He protects me,
我却一直让他失望
and all I ever do is let him down.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be okay.
- 不  - 我们都会没事
- No. - We're gonna be okay.
我们会拯救他
We're gonna go save him.
真的？怎样救？你和我
Oh, really? How? You and me
如何对抗整个严阵以待的第二个太阳？
against whatever the fuck Second Sun has waiting for us?
我们需要一支军队
We would need an entire army.
不，你不明白
No, listen, you don't understand.
杰克，一切都完了好吗？
It's over, Jack, okay?
我甚至不能对抗一小支“黄色领带”
I couldn't even handle a small band of Yellow Ties,
因为我只顾自己的世界
'cause I'm too busy in my own fucking world
- 我无法专注  - 对不起
just being distracted and... - Sorry.
你需要闭嘴，知道吗？
It's just that you need to shut up, okay?
你杀死了他们的皇后
You killed their queen.
这是你的军队
This is your army.
杰克…
Jack...
我们要往哪里走？
where do we go?
我们不知道第二个太阳在哪里
We have no idea where Second Sun is.
我抓到了一条小鱼
I caught a small fish.
你干了什么？
You did what?
我抓到了一条小鱼
I caught a small fish.
过来
Come here.
哥们，放我下来
Dude, get me down.
要抓到大鱼
To catch a big shark.
我不会告诉你任何东西
I'm not telling you anything.
杰克
Jack.
你真是一名出色的副手
You really are one hell of a gun caddy.
欢迎归来
Welcome back.
什么…
What the...
你糊涂了
You're confused.
你遭受了一点脑震荡，但是你会挺过去的
You have a slight concussion, but you'll survive.
我在哪里？
Where am I?
我们在你新的办公室
We're in your new office.
抽口烟？
Cigar?
我亲自卷的
I rolled them myself.
我还记得你最爱抽一口
I remember how much you liked them
在哈瓦那度蜜月的时候
on our honeymoon in Havana.
去你的，凯瑟琳
Fuck you, Catherine.
或许迟点吧
Maybe later.
我就直奔主题了
I'll cut to the chase.
桌子上是一份合同
That stack of papers on your desk is a contract.
如果你选择签名
Should you choose to sign it,
你就重新成为戈尔曼公司的总裁
you'll be reinstated as CEO of Gorman Enterprises.
我会掌握控股权益
I'll have a controlling interest,
但是你会是公司的面孔
but you'll be the face of the company.
你刚刚悬赏我的头颅，现在却…
You just issued a death warrant for me, and now you want to...
我从不打算杀死你，弗朗西斯
I never intended to kill you, Francis.
我是想摧毁赏金议会
The Council, yes.
当然还有那个贱女人，死神玛丽
That tart, Mary Death, obviously...
但是从来不想杀你
but never you.
不
No.
关于你，我有更大的计划
I have much bigger plans for you...
还有我们
for us.
你究竟在胡扯什么？
What the fuck are you talking about?
你看不见吗？
Don't you see?
末日创造了一个绝佳的商机
The apocalypse was the greatest business opportunity
那是前所未有的
that's ever come our way.
各种银行倒闭
It was the ultimate bankruptcy,
一笔勾销
a clean slate,
现在没有政府挡在我们面前
and now with no government to stand in our way,
没有联合体，没有最低工资和税收
there's no unions, no minimum wage and no taxes.
完全是纯净的资本主义
It's pure capitalism.
我们不必划分自由市场，弗朗西斯
We won't just corner the free market, Francis.
我们拥有自由市场
We'll own it.
这不是资本主义，凯瑟琳
That's not capitalism, Catherine.
这是一派胡言乱语
It's the wacked-out ramblings
因为一个女人失去她的理智
of a woman who's lost her bloody mind.
你说我失去理智？
I've lost my mind?
你自己带着一袋枪支各处奔走
You're the one riding around with a bag of guns
扮演着义务牛仔警察
playing vigilante cowboy.
虽然，我应该感谢你的
Although, actually I must thank you for that.
你和你的女朋友
You see, you and your little girlfriend
扫清了我们的竞争对手
were out there eliminating our competition,
最终，你的努力加快了我们的进程
so, in the end, your efforts simply sped up our schedule.
来和我经营这家公司吧，弗朗西斯
Run this company with me, Francis.
这是你唯一擅长的东西
It's the only thing you've ever been good at.
你是不是喜欢我了？
Are you coming on to me?
一切就是因为这个原因？
Is that what this is all about?
因为我不介意在桌子上打上一炮
You know, 'cause I'm not adverse to a quick romp on the desk
如果你言下之意是这样的话
if that's what you're saying.
我不想和你打炮，弗朗西斯
I don't want to fuck you, Francis.
我只想你和我一起建设这个帝国
I just want you to build this empire with me.
我要你带领我们的军队，开始征服世界
I want you to lead our army as we set out to conquer the world,
作为我们的形象勇士和总…
as our brand warrior and CE...
我们在开会呢！
We are in a meeting!
你怎样进来的…
How the hell did you get in...
你话太多了
You talk too much.
现在容我说句，“会议结束”
Now, I would have said, "Meeting's adjourned."
你打扮得很帅
You clean up nice.
你看起来一团糟，兔宝宝
You look like shit, fender bunny.
你给我带了枪吗？
You got a gun for me?
她没有，但我带了
Nope, but I do.
很高兴看到你，孩子
Good to see you, kid.
你们打算再缠绵一会呢
You guys gonna keep smooching,
还是打算打几下靶子？
or you want to go shoot some people?
# Well, I heard and I've been told #
# Of the things that you could do #
# Well, that you think nobody else #
# Can do half as good as you #
# I heard that you shake that thing well #
杰克，我没弹了
Jack, I'm out.
# Just want to know #
# Are you ready? #
# Ohh #
# Let's get on with it #
# Let your tears fall in line #
# Well, why don't you just let 'em fly? #
# Baby, just 'em fly #
# Come on #
# Hit it now #
# All right #
# You looking good, woman #
# That's it, sugar #
# Whaah #
# It's all right tonight #
# Yes #
# Look here
上弹！
Reload!
玛丽！
Mary!
不用客气
You're welcome.
不！
No!
玛丽，醒醒啊
Mary, wake up.
醒醒啊，玛丽
Wake up, Mary.
求你，别死
Please don't die.
振作点
Come on.
你吓死我了，兔宝宝
You scared me, fender bunny.
有时候它对女孩子来说值得使用
Sometimes it pays for a girl to be practical.
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
我不知道
I don't know.
我什么也感觉不到
I can't feel anything.
我看起来怎样？
How do I look?
比另一个家伙好多了
Better than the other guy.
她的头，没了
Her head is, like, just gone.
他们在上面呆了多久？
How long they been up there?
两周了
Two weeks.
听起来她好像还是不满足
She still don't sound mean enough.
不足为奇
Well, no wonder.
是谁教你安装配电器的？
Who taught you how to install a distributor?
我用螺栓连上去的
I bolted it on.
不单是螺栓这么简单，笨蛋
Takes more than just bolting it on, lug-head.
你得延迟引擎的第四级打火
You gotta retard the sparks four degrees.
否则，你会错过点火的时刻
Otherwise, it throws the timing off.
我觉得你是在胡吹
I think you're just making words up.
你从吉普赛人手中救了我
You saved me from them gypsies.
你的行为应该被答谢的
That's a deed that shouldn't go unrecognized.
这是你最后的啤酒
This is your last beer.
现在是你的最后的啤酒了
It's your last beer now.
谢谢，金波
Thanks, Jimbo.
听到吗？
Hear that?
尝起来像咪咪
Oh, that tastes like boobies.
车子怎么样？
How's the car?
随时可以出发
It's ready to go.
老杰克使尽了他的浑身解数
Old Jack here bought the best pony in my stable.
恶魔也快不过她了
She's mean enough to outrace the devil.
干得好，先生们
Nice job, boys.
你们还从小鱼探到什么口风？
Did you get anything else out of the fish?
挖出比目鱼的内脏似乎不错哦
Gutted the flounder pretty good.
我们知道了第二个太阳在什么地方
Told us there were Second Sun everywhere,
然后他供出了一个在费城海岸的基地
and then he gave up a base on the Philly coast.
好的 我会集合吉塞普人
All right. I'll rendezvous with the gypsies
然后和你们在费城碰头
and meet you in Philadelphia.
我还以为我们一起出发
Thought we were all going together.
帮我好好照顾他
Take care of him for me.
该死的，女人！
Damn it, woman!
你又一次割了我一刀！
You cut me deep! Again!
来咬我啊，老家伙
Come and get me, old man.